ICHIGO PRODUCTION SAITOU
(草莓娛樂,齊藤)
Maybe I should've hired you as a talent scout.
應該請妳當星探才對呢
A popular YouTuber as well as an influencer, Mem.
人氣YouTube頻道主 兼網紅MEM
I was surprised to know you were interested in idols.
沒想到妳竟然有興趣當偶像呢
You have 370,000 subscribers on your YouTube channel.
妳的YouTube 頻道訂閱人數有37萬
And 638,000 TikTok followers.
抖音關注人數有63萬8千
You seem to be very popular online.
在網上似乎頗有名氣呢
First, I'd like to first ask what agency you are with, Ms. Mem.
首先我想問一下 妳現在簽的是哪家事務所?
I'm actually self-employed as an online streamer.
我算是一個自僱的網路主播吧
Currently, I'm with an agency called FARM,
現在跟一家叫法姆的事務所合作
but I'm not registered with them, I work as a business partner.
但不是他們的所屬藝人 只是業務上的合作而已
I'm under a contract where I can freely take on jobs myself with no problems.
根據合約 我可以放心地自由選擇工作
I see.
原來如此
In that case, Ichigo Production will be offering idol work to you.
那樣的話,我們草莓娛樂 可以採用委託妳進行偶像業務的形式
We have many internet personalities too, so there's no problems with the contract.
我們公司也有很多網路紅人 合約方面應該沒什麼問題
It would be perfect for us.
這對我們而言算是駕輕就熟
But your expression tells me that there's something you need to say.
但看妳的表情 好像有什麼不得不說的事吧
Well, I've got a hunch.
不過,我也心裡有數啦
You're lying about your age, aren't you?
妳謊報年齡了,對吧?
Can you tell?
看得出來嗎?
Yes, you look very young based on your build,
嗯,雖然妳的骨架小,看起來很年輕
but you can't fool my eyes.
但那是逃不過我的眼睛的
But you don't need to worry.
不過妳也不用太擔心啦
It's very common for freelancing girls to lie a few years about their age.
自由身的女藝人 虛報自己的年齡是常見的事
I don't really mind.
我不介意喔
Are you sure?
真的嗎?
I'm so glad.
那太好了
So, how old are you really?
所以,妳實際年齡是幾歲?
Um... well...
那個...這個嘛...
I'm actually...
其實我...
Mm-hm.
嗯
You really stretched it!
也差太多了吧!
I apologize!
真的非常抱歉!
If you're officially 18 years old, you got some major guts.
虛報18歲的話...妳膽子還真大啊
Please don't count!
拜託別數了!
How many years did you subtract? Like three?
差了幾歲啊?三歲左右嗎?
Double that.
兩倍
You sure stretched it!
真的差太多啦!
Wait, so you're 24?
所以妳是24?
I was 24 until spring.
24啊,春天以前還是
Which means you're 25. Don't try to struggle your way out at this point.
也就是25嘛 事到如今就別再掙扎了
So you were on the show as a teenager at 25? You got monstrous mental strength.
25歲了還自稱女高中生去上節目? 心理素質有夠強大的
There's a reason to this!
我是有苦衷的
My dream was to become an idol since I was little.
我從小的夢想就是成為偶像
But I was raised by a single mom and I also have two little brothers.
但我家是單親家庭,我還有兩個弟弟
So I felt that I should find a job right away.
我本來也想直接出來找工作的
But Mama told me...
但媽媽卻跟我說...
Don't worry, just chase your dreams!
別想太多,去追逐妳的夢想吧
Mama will be with you to help!
媽媽會陪妳一起努力的
After that, I started applying to auditions.
於是,我就去參加徵選了
I even made it to a major agency's last screening.
甚至還進到了大公司的最終選拔
But during my 3rd year in high school...
可是,在我高三那年
Mama worked too hard and was hospitalized.
媽媽因為工作過勞入院了
I needed money,
由於急需用錢
so I took a break from high school and worked at all kinds of jobs.
我就決定休學,打了各式各樣的工
Thanks to that, I was able to send my brothers to college,
正因如此,弟弟們才能夠上大學
and my mom got better too.
媽媽的病情也好轉了
But by that time, I was already 23.
但那個時候,我已經23歲了
You know how you're treated as a granny at 20 in this world?
在這個世界,一到20歲 就被當成老太婆了,不是嗎?
Every audition application said, "Any female up to 20 years of age."
每個徵選的申請資格 都是不超過20歲的女生
By the time I was in a state to chase my dreams,
等到我有能力追逐夢想的時候
I wasn't at an age to chase them anymore.
我卻已經錯過追夢的年齡了
I began streaming after losing my way of becoming an idol.
知道自己當不成偶像之後 我就轉向當主播了
And I was still on break from high school at the time,
那時候我還是高中休學的狀態嘛
so I joked that I was a current high school girl.
所以就用女高中生的感覺拍片了
But then I got surprisingly popular.
結果居然大受歡迎
And I gained subscribers like crazy.
訂閱數漲得超快
Then I couldn't back out anymore!
變得一發不可收拾了
I continued like that for two years and here I am today.
之後一直維持了兩年 變成現在這個情況
I know, this isn't okay.
果然不行吧
I lied about seven years, and it would be a major problem if it got out.
虛報了七歲呢 哪天暴露的話,麻煩可就大了
A 25-year-old as an idol could never...
25歲當偶像什麼的...
That's not true.
才不是那樣呢
Mem-cho!
MEM啾!
The real thing! So cute!
是本人耶!好可愛!
I heard the whole story.
剛才說的我都聽到了
Arima.
有馬
I'm also someone who was scorned for their age,
我也是會因為年齡而被瞧不起的人
so I can relate a little.
所以能稍微理解妳的心情
It doesn't seem like a little.
看起來不止稍微啊
Once I got older in elementary school, my child acting agency kicked me out.
那家童星經紀公司 也是在我一上高年級就把我開除了
It really pisses me off!
真是氣死人了
What?
什麼?
Mrs. Miyako!
美彌子小姐!
That's why I never said no.
所以我也沒拒絕啊
And you, Ruby?
露比呢?
Of course!
當然沒問題!
Age doesn't matter in becoming an idol!
當偶像這回事無關年齡
Because you can't stop anyone from dreaming!
因為這種憧憬是無法停止的
Welcome to B Komachi!
歡迎加入B小町!
Yeah... Thank you.
嗯,請多指教
There goes my sister with her sugarcoating again.
我家妹妹又在說這種漂亮話了
Arima, take care of Ruby and Mem for me.
有馬,露比和MEM就拜託妳了
Shut up, don't talk to me so casually.
吵死了,別隨隨便便跟我搭話
Go take care of Akane Kurokawa.
你就去照顧你的黑川茜吧
You womanizing steward!
花花公子
I'm gonna keep this group together even without you telling me.
不用你說,我也會搞好這個組合
Hey, let's go out to eat right now.
好了,我們去吃東西吧
Let's go!
走吧
What's with these girls? They're so warmhearted!
這兩個孩子是怎麼回事? 也太親切了吧
And like that, Mem-cho joined our group.
就這樣,MEM啾加入了我們的組合
And the newly formed B Komachi made its official start.
新生B小町正式開始活動
Aww, Love For Real ended.
啊,《現戀》結束了呢
Hey, how did you feel seeing your brother kissing on the show?
問妳喔,看到哥哥在節目上接吻 心裡有什麼感受啊?
How did I feel?
有什麼感受?
Can there be anything other than super mixed feelings?
除了超複雜以外 還能有什麼感受呢?
I thought so.
我想也是
It was five times as awkward as watching a brother and sister kissing on TV.
比起在電視上看到兄妹接吻的場面 還要尷尬五倍左右
Eek...
真是的
Ruby, you'll probably meet Akane one day too.
露比遲早也會見到小茜的吧
Since she is your brother's girlfriend.
畢竟她是妳哥哥的女朋友嘛
Girlfriend...
女朋友...
But Aqua's feelings toward Akane is probably...
但阿奎亞對小茜的感情一定是...
Is this about Love For Real?
在聊《現戀》嗎?
Oh, yeah.
是啊
You knew about it, Ms. Shiranui?
不知火同學也知道這個節目啊?
Well, someone I know is on it after all. It was interesting.
畢竟有認識的人出演嘛,還挺好看的
You don't need to be so considerate.
也不用說這種場面話啦
There were nothing but pretty boys and cute girls in it.
出演的全是帥哥美女
It was great eye candy.
真的很養眼呢
Eye candy?!
-養眼?
I didn't think a top star would say something like that too.
沒想到頂級明星也會說這種話呢
Who doesn't like pretty faces?
應該沒人不喜歡長得好看的人吧?
It pleased my eyes so much, I think my eyesight got better by 0.5.
實在是大飽眼福 感覺視力都變好了0.5度
She says some funny stuff!
-她說話好有趣!
Personally, I liked Mem-cho's maiden face.
我個人很喜歡MEM啾 那副戀愛中少女的表情
If I were one of the boys, I would've totally made her mine.
如果我是其中一個男生的話 我絕對會把她推倒
I wish they would have put more spirit into seducing her.
好希望他們能多花點心思追求她啊
Ms. Shiranui is very cool on TV,
不知火同學在電視上那麼高冷
but I didn't know she was like this in private.
沒想到私底下是這樣的啊
But I hear this is common actually.
不過,這種情況好像挺常見的
Men tend to feel rivalry toward funny women before romantic feelings,
面對風趣幽默的女性 男性會在產生戀愛感覺之前
making it difficult for them to become popular.
先出現抗拒的心理 這樣的女性很難提高人氣
So they're not allowed to joke while they have on an innocent image.
所以擁有清純形象的女藝人 都會被禁止耍寶喔
What an ugly fact.
好討厭的話題啊
Maybe it's because I'm watching it from the cast's acquaintance view,
或許是因為我認識阿奎亞同學 看的時候視角不一樣
but it made my heart race.
感覺超心動的
I'm sure everyone else feels the same too.
不過大家應該都有一樣的感覺吧
I hear Aqua is super popular with the girls in the General Department.
聽說阿奎亞哥哥 在一般學科那邊很受女生歡迎喔
Some girls in our department are interested in him too.
在我們演藝科 好像也有一些女生對他有好感
But he supposedly has a girlfriend,
可是他表面上已經有女友了
so I'm sure everyone will just watch over for now.
所以大家暫時都還在觀望吧
In fact, Love For Real's following is very high,
實際上《現戀》相當受矚目
and it must've been a major influence for my brother's future.
肯定會對哥哥的未來造成巨大的影響
But it also made a significant impact on B Komachi.
不過,這個節目 也給B小町帶來了重大影響
With Mem-cho joining,
MEM啾加入之後
we're now able to create more professional videos for our channel.
我們的頻道 總算可以做出更專業的影片了
Wow! We reached 10,000 subscribers!
哇!訂閱人數破萬了!
Well, I created the user flow from my channel too,
畢竟都用上我的頻道來吸引流量了
so this much should be expected.
這種程度也是理所當然的吧
It feels... really official!
有種官方頻道的感覺呢
If it isn't official, what else would it be?
本來就是我們的官方頻道啊
We only have self-introduction videos uploaded,
現在上傳的只有我們自我介紹的影片
so I'd like to put up our music videos as soon as we can.
可以的話 我想盡快上傳我們的MV之類的
But how is our music-related stuff going right now?
歌曲那方面現在怎麼樣了?
Looks like the CEO's asking an artist she knows to write it.
社長好像在請認識的作曲家幫忙寫歌
We can't do anything until the music's ready.
歌曲完成之前,我們什麼也做不了吧
It's still a long way ahead, so let's just sit back and wait.
還早得很呢,放輕鬆,慢慢等吧
Well, we can't do that.
這可不行
Did you forget that we're B Komachi?
妳忘了我們是B小町嗎?
B Komachi has B Komachi songs, right?
B小町有B小町的歌曲,對吧?
Oh yeah! There's no problems if we use the old songs!
對喔,用以前的曲子就沒問題啦
Right!
沒錯
Mem-cho, you're a genius!
MEM啾真是個天才!
Tsk. So they noticed.
討厭,居然注意到了
There's a lot we can do right now!
我們現在能做的事多得不得了
If we waste too much time, I'll hit my thirties!
要是再繼續浪費時間 我很快就要奔三啦
So self-deprecating...
好自虐
The first and foremost duty as an idol!
偶像的首要任務
The idol's most splendorous and toughest part...
也就是偶像最光彩奪目 但也最艱難的部分
We're gonna learn the dance choreography!
我們要開始練舞囉!
LET'S B KOMACHI DANCE LESSON!!
(跟著B小町 舞蹈訓練跳起來!)
There's 30 songs with choreography that have footage left.
有影音資料的曲子一共有30首
Don't tell me they want to learn all of it.
別告訴我要統統記下來啊
I can't keep up with these two idol otakus' motivation.
我快跟不上那兩個偶像宅的幹勁了啦
Why did I say that I'll become an idol?
我為什麼會答應當偶像啊?
Good work.
辛苦了
Thank...
謝...
I don't need it! Go away!
我不需要!滾一邊去啦!
You've been acting like this toward me for a while now.
妳最近對我的態度一直是這樣呢
I know that you mouth off and have a bad attitude, but...
我知道妳說話不好聽 態度也不好,不過...
at this rate, I'll get hurt too.
老是這樣的話,我也會受傷的
What's with that? Huh?
什麼嘛?在說什麼?
You were the one who...
明明是你先...
You're the one...
是你...
Aqua!
阿奎亞
Me telling you this story now is like digging up someone's grave.
我接下來要說的事 就像是在挖開死者的墳墓一樣
Why do you want to know about Ai so much?
你為什麼那麼想知道愛的事情呢?
I'm a fan of hers.
我是她的粉絲
A hopeless one.
無可救藥的那種
Do you need a reason beyond that?
還需要什麼別的理由嗎?
The illusion seen by fans shatter once they know the reality.
一旦知道了真實的模樣 粉絲們腦海裡的幻想就會破滅
There is no exception to this.
無一例外
Showbiz is pretty much a bluffing contest.
演藝圈說白了 就是一場虛張聲勢的比賽
An alluring subject tells an alluring lie
用有魅力的素材來編造有魅力的謊言
in order to stage a charismatic figure that doesn't really exist in real life.
呈現出不存在於現實世界的人格魅力
What most people do in job hunting to get into good companies
求職者為了進入好公司而做的那些事
is what we do for business.
正是我們所做的生意
Even so, I'd still like to know.
即便如此,我還是想知道
If you say you're a fan, it's best not to know.
如果真的是粉絲的話 還是不知道比較好喔
But no one ever listens.
但人總是那麼固執
I connected with Ai and introduced her some jobs like I told you before.
我之前跟你說過 我因為因緣際會給愛介紹了不少工作
Back then, Ai was just a country girl who just moved here from the sticks.
那時候的愛 還只是個剛從老家出來的鄉下女孩
Her level of professionalism was low, she'd never try to fit in,
沒什麼專業意識 也不嘗試融入周邊的圈子
and she'd come to work wearing cheap clothes that never suited her.
總是穿著 跟自己不搭的廉價衣服到片場工作
She was just a child.
不過是個小鬼而已
So, I thought it might help her somehow,
然後呢,我想說可能對她有幫助
so I introduced her to this one theater's workshop.
就給她介紹了某個劇團的培訓班
A workshop?
培訓班?
It's one that I used to be a part of during college.
我念大學的時候曾經加入過那個劇團
It's called Theater Lalalai.
拉拉萊劇團
The theater group that Akane belongs to.
也就是小茜所屬的劇團
It wasn't that famous at the time though.
不過那時候他們的名氣沒那麼大
They say love changes people.
都說愛情能改變一個人
That's probably the place...
那裡應該就是...
where Ai fell in love.
愛墜入愛河的地方吧
Ever since Ai joined that workshop, she started to care about her appearance.
自從參加那個培訓班之後 她開始在意自己的打扮
And she would ask me where the good restaurants were.
還問我有沒有什麼推薦的好餐廳
Of course I couldn't tell who her dates were,
雖然我也不知道對方是誰
but I remember she suddenly looked all grown-up.
但我記得 她彷彿一夕之間變得很有女人味
If you're curious, I'll introduce you to Lalalai's superintendent.
有興趣的話 我可以給你介紹拉拉萊劇團的負責人
You'll surely get closer to the answer you're looking for there.
在那裡的話 你一定會更接近你想知道的答案吧
Why would you go that far for me?
你為什麼願意做到這種地步?
I'm just a failed actor with no achievements whatsoever.
我只不過是個 沒什麼成就的三流演員罷了
Because I see potential in you.
我在你身上看到了可能性
This industry is all about give-and-take.
這圈子就是一個討賣人情的世界
As you already know, in Japanese showbiz,
相信你也知道,在日本的演藝圈
the give-and-take between the agencies and production companies affect the casting.
事務所和製作方之間的人情關係 很大程度地左右了出演陣容
And depending on the cast, the profit changes by the hundred millions.
而根據出演陣容的不同 最終收益會以數億為單位發生變化
This 40,000-yen sushi will feel like nothing
這種四萬日圓左右的壽司套餐
compared to how much money will be exchanged.
跟那樣的金錢交易相比 簡直不值一提
By you owing me a favor now,
我現在賣你一個人情
once you become a star and you hit your prime,
萬一你以後成了一線明星,大紅大紫
I can have a big advantage in the casting battles to come.
我就能在日後出演陣容的戰爭中 取得巨大的優勢
This is what a producer does.
這就是製作人的工作
Of course, I don't do this just to you.
當然,你並非唯一的投資對象
I see potential in Kana Arima and Mem-cho too.
我在有馬佳奈和MEM啾身上 也看到了可能性
Looks like you kids have started something interesting.
你們好像在進行很有意思的企劃呢
I hear you guys revived that B Komachi group.
聽說你們把B小町復活了啊
I feel that all of you are quite the promising investment.
我覺得你們 都是很有前途的投資對象呢
You don't mean...
難道說...
Japan Idol Festival?!
-日本偶像音樂節?
Yeah, the producer from Love For Real says he has connections.
嗯,《現戀》的製作人說他有管道
So if we're interested, he said he'll squeeze us in.
如果我們有興趣的話 他可以幫我們牽線
But JIF's next month, right?!
但那個音樂節在下個月舉辦吧?
No way! We're not prepared at all.
不行...我們什麼都沒準備好呢
If some newbies like us suddenly went on a big stage like that--
像我們這樣的新人 一下子登上那麼大的舞台...
Let's do it!
去嘛!
It's JIF, the JIF!
那可是日本偶像音樂節啊!
Wouldn't it be cool if the new B Komachi's first concert is at a big stage like that?
新生B小町的首次現場演唱 能上那麼大的舞台,不是超棒的嗎?
But we'll definitely create a bad impression to those around us.
可是,我們肯定會給人 留下不好的印象
I'm sure they'll say connection this and connection that.
一定會有人說我們是靠關係什麼的
Don't worry!
沒問題的
We're the successors of the legendary group, B Komachi!
我們可是傳奇團體B小町的繼任者啊
You're the one who started saying that on your own.
那也是妳自己一廂情願冠上的名號啊
But in reality, there's no way we let this chance go.
以實際考量 這是個不容錯失的大好機會喔
A normal group spends long hard years to finally get to this stage.
一般的團體不知得拼命活動多少年 才能登上這個舞台
So if we don't do this now, what are we working towards?
要是現在不把握這個機會 那我們當偶像是為了什麼啊?
Well, that's true.
說得也是啦
If we're gonna do it, let's do it.
想幹就幹吧
This is work after all.
畢竟這也算是工作嘛
Okay, it's decided!
-好,就這麼定了
Then it's time!
關於那個嘛
We gotta decide now.
是時候該做決定了
What?
決定什麼?
Who to have as B Komachi's center role.
決定B小町的C位由誰來擔任啊
Is it that important?
這有那麼重要嗎?
Who cares who the center is?
隨便哪位都行吧
It is important!
-這很重要!
The center is the idol group's star!
C位是偶像團體的焦點
The cute one who can sing and dance, they're the face of the group!
是能歌善舞的可愛女孩 也是團體的門面擔當
It's the most important position!
那可是最重要的位置
Right?
-對吧?
You two really get along.
妳們關係真不錯啊
So, does anyone want to do it?
所以,有人想當嗎?
I-I'm not saying that I wanna do it, but if everyone insists...
也不是說我很想當啦 但如果大家堅持的話...
This probably has to be the oldest and wisest.
果然還是得選有歷練的人吧
I don't wanna do it, but my experience should help bring the group together.
我沒有很想當喔 但如果我的人生經驗能帶領團體...
You both look like you really wanna do it.
明明兩個都是一臉超想當的表情
I mean, shouldn't it be me who's good at dancing?
果然還是應該 由擅長跳舞的我來當吧?
Well, no, it should be me who's used to the media and well-experienced!
不對,應該由習慣在媒體上露面 經驗豐富的我來當才對
If you put it that way, that would make it Senpai.
要這麼說的話 應該由學姐來當才對喔
Since her "Green Pepper Exercise" took 1st place on the charts
畢竟她曾經 以《大青椒體操》拿下公信榜一位
and she was all over music shows.
還一直在音樂節目上登場呢
Wow, what a throwback!
哇,超懷念的
Don't bring up my embarrassing past!
不要隨便翻開人家的黑歷史!
Let's start the "Green Pepper Exercise"!
大青椒體操,要開始了喔
Eat green peppers and become Superman
吃塊大青椒,變身超人吧
Everybody dance and become Peter Pan
一起來跳舞,變成彼得潘
You know how she sang a little off-key...
而且還唱得有點走音的感覺
Right? That was so childlike and cute!
對吧?特別有童真,超可愛的
They made me dance to it in kindergarten.
幼兒園的時候,老師還讓我們跳過呢
Hey, try singing it!
妳來唱一下嘛
No way!
我絕對不要
I know that I suck at singing!
自己唱得不好這件事 我還是有自知之明的
I mean, don't you have to be able to sing as the center?
C位果然還是得看唱功吧?
That's true, it doesn't look good if the center doesn't hold a mic.
確實,身為C位卻沒拿手麥 也太不像話了吧
How despicable.
好卑鄙啊
How about whoever gets a higher score in karaoke gets it?!
就用卡拉OK的分數 來決定C位,怎麼樣?
All right!
就這麼辦
Senpai, you too, right?!
學姐,妳也會去吧?
I'll pass.
我就不去了
What? But...
嗯?可是...
Stupid, the center is the group's face, right?
笨蛋,C位是團體的門面擔當吧?
If you put me as the center, this group won't get any popular.
要是讓我當C位的話 對團體的人氣可沒什麼幫助喔
That's not true.
也不能這麼說吧
There's enough evidence to prove it.
證據已經很充足了
Even after my one-hit wonder child star years were over,
在紅極一時的童星時代結束之後
you think that I'd only be acting while I clung to this industry for years?
我還在這個業界掙扎多年 妳們不會以為我只有在演戲吧?
I tried a variety of fields, but never got popular.
我也嘗試過不同的領域 但始終沒什麼人氣
I put the agency that gave me work for my child star fame in the red,
有公司看在我童星時期的名氣的份上 給我工作,我卻只會讓他們虧錢
but I made sure to take my pay, so I could feed myself.
但我還是會確保自己拿到薪資 好混一口飯吃
To sum it up, there are no fans following Kana Arima!
總而言之,有馬佳奈是沒有粉絲的喔
I totally agree! Who'd wanna put money into a foul-mouthed, jaded woman like me?
不想花錢在我這種沒有口德 性格又差的女人身上,這點我超認同
Oh, that's right, I'll Go with Sweet Today was in the red too, huh?!
對了,《今甜》電視劇 好像也是赤字喔
Mem-cho, you have a ton of subscribers.
MEM啾的訂閱人數多得驚人
Ruby, you at least got a great face, and your innocence will probably win fans.
露比只靠臉蛋就能獲得關注 天真爛漫的性格也會很受歡迎
Besides...
而且
the ones who are likable are honest cute girls like you two.
討人喜歡的人 都是像妳們一樣坦率又可愛的孩子
Not a difficult and bitter woman like me.
而不是我這樣麻煩又難相處的女人
You can just think of me as decoration.
妳們當我是來湊人數的就可以了
Karaoke or whatever, just choose the center between you two.
用卡拉OK或什麼方式都行 妳們兩個自己決定誰當C位吧
Senpai, you're really sulky lately.
感覺學姐最近老是自暴自棄呢
Did something bad happen?
發生什麼不好的事了嗎?
Not really.
沒什麼
Don't worry!
別擔心啦
Even my brother who never compliments people said that you're cute.
連我那個不怎麼誇人的哥哥 都說學姐妳可愛呢
You're not difficult or bitter at all.
妳怎麼會麻煩又難相處呢?
But he said that to Mem-cho in Love For Real too.
但他在《現戀》 也對MEM啾說了一樣的話啊
What a difficult and bitter woman...
真是麻煩又難相處的女人
You always have to argue.
老是愛唱反調
It must be tough for whoever dates someone like this.
跟妳交往的男人肯定會很辛苦吧
Well, most celebrities are difficult people.
好啦,藝人當中 本來就很多麻煩的人啊
Wait, Aqua's the one who invited these two to join.
等等,這兩個人 都是阿奎亞開口邀請加入的吧
I don't like how I can gradually see what kind of women my brother likes.
漸漸能看出哥哥喜歡的女生類型 這種感覺好討厭啊
Come join us later.
妳待會要來喔
Okay.
嗯
KARAOKE
(卡拉OK)
57 POINTS LET'S WORK A LITTLE HARDER!
(57分,繼續努力)
43 POINTS OH... OKAY. TRY HARDER?
(43分,加油?)
I'm surprised you took up this challenge with a score like that!
就這點分數,虧妳還敢接受挑戰啊
Y-You too, you're in the quirky category!
妳也只是不好不壞的程度啊
Idols are all about uniqueness!
偶像看的是個性
Even being quirky has value!
不好不壞也是有商品價值的
But if you suck, you can't help that!
但純粹唱得爛的話就沒得救啦
The joy of watching a poor singer get gradually better live!
看著唱功不好的孩子一步步成長 那份喜悅才是難以言喻的
I'm thinking of providing this to the fans! There's a story there!
我就是想給粉絲提供這樣的體驗 這都是設定好的劇情
I should've practiced singing more seriously.
之前就應該更認真練習唱歌嘛
We both need training!
我們倆都需要特訓呢
Please don't put me on the same level as you.
別把我跟妳 歸類在同一個等級好不好?
Why don't we take a quick break?
稍微休息一下吧
Right. Let's sing a light song as a breather.
也對,讓我們喘口氣 找一首輕鬆的歌吧
Why don't we sing Senpai's "Green Pepper Exercise"?
不如就唱學姐的《大青椒體操》吧
Ruby, you got a pretty evil personality. I honestly like it.
露比妳的性格也有點那個呢 說實話,我還挺喜歡的
- Oh. - Hm?
-哦 -嗯?
Arima released a lot of songs after "Green Pepper Exercise."
原來有馬在《大青椒體操》之後 也發行過不少別的歌啊
I never knew.
我都不知道呢
Wanna listen to it?
要聽聽看嗎?
Yeah.
好
KANA ARIMA
(滿月...!有馬佳奈)
Seriously, what a difficult person.
還真是個麻煩的傢伙啊
And she says she sucks?
居然還說自己唱得不好
97 POINTS
(97分)
Isn't she too hard on herself?
是不是對自己太嚴苛啦?
AMAZING!!
(97分,太厲害了!)
Subtitle translation by: Kanami Kitabayashi
字幕翻譯:蔡曉琳